shutage: hi
shutage: say hi back
xaviergregor: hello
programmer42: hey
FargioFarmani: Please don't abort the stream like last time @georgehotz
amratesh: George acknowledge me please?
FigurativelyVyres: First time I'm early to a stream Pog
programmer42: what are you working on ?
rawfael: Rawfael subscribed with Twitch Prime.
benchai18: He’s alive
amratesh: I'm from India. and I'm in EU rn. Twitch took away my subscribe button and gift button
cybermajestic: hello)
l1ttlemtman: hello
benchai18: Nice coq George. The fuck u been
cybermajestic: show us your comma device
Kaotprox: nice sweatshirt
l1ttlemtman: metamath is shit
Caene: limmySteel
l1ttlemtman: Isabelle is king
amratesh: Guys watching the steam you do realize what George is doing right? he's streaming himself solving the problems and creating the startups/programs he wants to create, so he can train the "algorithm"
eduardoadf1: have you watched bjarne podcast?
amratesh: Stream*
benchai18: GeoCoq
euranymous: hi George
qujoga: Are u a vim power user?
amratesh: George you should stream more. the creator of Vines is streaming like 24/7
benchai18: Damn there are zero immature pple like me in this channel
tfue_is_dog_shit: no 1 is good at regex lol
Yemtex: !time
amratesh: sorry
mariodose: hi @georgehotz
Yemtex: what time is it at your place george ?
sanaki13: its so small
euranymous: !uptime
amratesh: George, have you seen Will Kwan?
euranymous: mod!???
tfue_is_dog_shit: What does an intern and a senior both have in common? They both search how to work with dates,regex etc..
zoki_macola: @amratesh Where can i watch him
dec3r: @georgehotz do you have any experience with agda?
itsChoudhry: @amratesh Hey I watch his videos his videos are pretty good
amratesh: I'm waiting for "the guy" who mentions Geo's keyboard lol
tfue_is_dog_shit: LUL
eduardoadf1: TriHard
amratesh: @itschoudhry GeoHot is doing the same thing. maybe he doesn't know it yet or maybe he doesn't want to be vocal about it
itsChoudhry: How long til people shitpost asking about what mouse he is using all the time
erichtp: George are you a fan of teejayx6
itsChoudhry: @amratesh What do you mean the same thing?
Keyeh: cmonBruh
NonTrivial778: niiiiiiiceeee
NonTrivial778: Cool stream brother
swsh: print debugging LUL
amratesh: Umm, feeding the universe/algorithm/ai. whatever you like calling it
euranymous: he uses vim and tmux mouse is rarely used
crashnk: laskiP laskiP laskiP laskiP laskiP
SSayMyName: what about keyboard?
euranymous: George what about copyright issues???
Svr123456789: hi George
shutchie: !uptime
Svr123456789: rip me 30seconds of ads
Keyeh: this is twitch, there is no copyright
Keyeh: only on the vods though LUL
caylakyazilimci: What is your pc model?
amratesh: @itschoudhry are you one of the 50 people who get to watch Kwans streams? he doesn't stream on twitch or mixer. he has a secret platform. pretty selective about who gets in
zgamer0123: Mode Beast ON
bloodborne24: you can play all the copyrighted stuff u want, they just mute part of the vod
ooMariaoo: @amratesh ohh D:
l1ttlemtman: thanks for banning me on discord btw
euranymous: yeah I was talking about that
nautzz: hell yes catchin the shit live
shrek_361: subbed
ooMariaoo: @amratesh whos kwans
itsChoudhry: @amratesh nope, but I still don't understand about what you mean by they are doing the same thing. You said something about the universe and the algorithm?? I'm confused.
ZemkeCWT: Anybody knows the what applications the icons in the title bar refer to? I know the left one is OBS.
komocode_: what happened to learning Unity?
Dervolleschlanke: what is he even doing
Svr123456789: lot of childs in this code... We got him !
erichtp: wait did he prove 1 1 = 2 ?
amratesh: lol NVM I'm sorry for bringing it up. Geohot knows what's up ;)
Svr123456789: 1 1=11 dude
bloodborne24: hes proving math is real with programming
SSayMyName: do a typing test
shrek_361: In the future could you do some projects with tensorflow?
itsChoudhry: @Dervolleschlanke Bro read about metamath online it's some freaky shit
SSayMyName: how many wpm
erichtp: ice chewing DansGame
amratesh: @oomariaoo Will Kwan
itsChoudhry: @amratesh -_- I guess I'm not cool enough
joker2k999: Dat metaMath coq tho...
whichtom: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
amratesh: you're cool. just not deep enough inside the rabbit hole
Yeahsper: what is a coq?
ooMariaoo: @amratesh ohh thanks :)
euranymous: basic programming ooh the irony
amratesh: can you please look into the lens more? sorry if it sounds like I'm trying to tell you stuff to do
Keyeh: tsucc Kreygasm
itsChoudhry: @amratesh ah okay maybe some day. I'm more deep in butthole right now
amratesh: lol
imaginenation: Geo how's the Instagram dream going?
erichtp: Fuck instagram no verification
itsChoudhry: @imaginenation He's moved on he said it's too much work and he got bored of it
amratesh: @imaginenation it will blow up he needs to do some additional things to make the "algorithm" happy to push his Instagram
imaginenation: damn
imaginenation: there's people with 9k followers verified which is funny
amratesh: Instagram verification is a black box. with humans that can override. geohot needs to make the algorithm happy
equalizer_____: Privet Geo
jagger_rsw: *polish* notation, take that world
Keyeh: reversed polish actually
imaginenation: I mean he can definitely do it. I was looking forward to geohot social media domination :(
amratesh: @georgehotz you do realize that even if you create your own math you cannot prove true=false
amratesh: maybe for the next stream? I would love to see it happen
imaginenation: that would be cute
Dzemixx: what exactly is he building ?
amratesh: lol I don't mean writing an axiom that essentially says 0=1
imaginenation: nothing to be honest
swsh: i've tried to prove excluded middle theorem from double negation axiom in Lean yesterday, damn that was hard
Dzemixx: oh
RSPwner_: are you using screen for multiple tabs?
Joemerlino: Just bought a comma ai off ebay, but didn’t knew chffr was discontinued :(
Vjasal: call it quick maths
Yeahsper: What language is this written in?
StrickenDown: every program on mac looks so much better GUI wise than windows it's unreal
imaginenation: true windows is a bit weird at times
amratesh: lol idiots
sk84uhlivin: FrankerZ
imaginenation: there is no usefulness to metamaths or is there? @georgehotz
prafaeltsantos: hello ❤
cod4TV: @Yeahsper Python.
amratesh: @imaginenation let's just say you can write a universe in metamath
RSPwner_: @georgehotz are you using screen for multiple tabs?
cod4TV: Every sunday morning, is this the new stream schedule?
imaginenation: @amratesh what you said is so abstract it's retarded lol
amratesh: lol
TCarriesYou: why does this guy not use GUI code editors!
imaginenation: idk
lidermaury: real rappers drink kool-aid, not tea
amratesh: I feel you @georgehotz hard to name these things
imaginenation: @georgehotz what is the usefulness for metamath?
CaptainAshtar: brain practice
prafaeltsantos: @tcarriesyou becouse vim tmux is the real goat
unluckychickenn: unluckychickenn subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! tmaBeard tmaHerz
amratesh: @imaginenation the usefulness of metamath is that you can write a verifier for metamath inside metamath
imaginenation: but don't you already have verifiers in mathematical logic?
maverick_twitch_: hello
cod4TV: why verifying 2 2=4?
imaginenation: unless that metamath verifier offers some significant advantage
maverick_twitch_: why you not work on climate change
CaptainAshtar: because you can verify it in a lot of ways
nautzz: i havent watched anything other than ur twitchcoq stuff
imaginenation: @georgehotz you gotta learn how the views algorithm work.
maverick_twitch_: lol
imaginenation: 😂
Richardable: Me neither I only come to twitch to watch this
CaptainAshtar: so if you want to test new language like metamath you will choose something simple to acquire the skill then continue with big stuff
imaginenation: his twitch slam stuff was great
maverick_twitch_: i am building a transpiler
theendri99: p = 1-q
swsh: modus_ponens: p -> (p -> q) -> q
jmc516: What is the name of the tea u drink?
amratesh: just green tea
CaptainAshtar: @jmc516 really does it matter?
jmc516: Yeah actually
CaptainAshtar: why?
jmc516: Green tea varies widely
cod4TV: Pure Leaf Tea
maverick_twitch_: tea
Mario_G: sup @georgehotz how are u today?
jmc516: There's also like a billion different types of tea
maverick_twitch_: not billion
jmc516: How many then? U count?
CaptainAshtar: so what happens when he tell you the brand i don't get it?
TheAwesomezter: this is not basic programming wtf
jmc516: I try it? Why do u care lol
maverick_twitch_: there's many
jmc516: It's not complicated
maverick_twitch_: whats (2*5)/500 ?
amratesh: @georgehotz I just want to ask you 3 questions. it will be a private thing between you and I. and it will take only as long as you take to reply. and I like only absolutes. I won't ask you vague BS. you wanna give me sometime from your life for it. I believe in you as much as I believe in me
Unsavable: bruh
CaptainAshtar: wtf
maverick_twitch_: @amratesh just cuz you subbed
maverick_twitch_: :(
puffnfresh: modus ponens is function application
amratesh: Nah just because
maverick_twitch_: i know you wanna ask if he likes anime
maverick_twitch_: :D
rawfael: teach us how to pick up girls, no programming today
maverick_twitch_: @rawfael become rich
puffnfresh: variable out of a term?
Lakimadscientist: teach us how to be chad
Acles123: what do you eating george
Blintike: hahaha :D
puffnfresh: I only joined two minutes ago so I'm lost
amratesh: lol
bloodborne24: just be chad 4Head
lidermaury: thats why George starts hitting gym
jmc516: Ice is code for something
puffnfresh: but sounds like function abstraction
cod4TV: Workout stream, PLZ!
Lakimadscientist: cooking stream
puffnfresh: functions?
grimers: have you managed to prove a theorem in metamath yet?
maverick_twitch_: streams him sleeping in a gym
itsChoudhry: You don't need strength to pick up girls... just have super low standards and keep talking to strangers
amratesh: George can you make math that checks out in our universe using less than Paeno's axioms?
maverick_twitch_: i love meth
maverick_twitch_: less math
puffnfresh: sounds like function application
amratesh: I can only imagine how stressful it is for him trying to break math while god/ai is watching
maverick_twitch_: why is it green
Bitcoin__: Hey
amratesh: It's like twitch ___...___
maverick_twitch_: streams him eating ice cubes
puffnfresh: I don't know what system you're working in, but I assume functions bare terms which contain variables
ET_515: Cheer5 Hello
puffnfresh: functions *are* terms
jagger_rsw: don't you feel like quitting this programming business and going on a journey around the world instead? :)
maverick_twitch_: programming is just but var and func
xxdvxx: hi
numberedsamas: what am i watching right now?
numberedsamas: what are you programming with?
xxdvxx: waiting for a aHA moment
MorningScifi: If we get this right, the computer can prove some crazy stuff, win us the Fields Medal, and we can soak up all the glory
amratesh: @georgehotz a better way to approach this could be not using Paeno's Axioms.
amratesh: and write fewer Axioms that can do math which checks out in our universe
aaronfriedland: mizkifSat
zoki_macola: is metamath useful because there are complex things that cant be proved on paper
MorningScifi: Proof by contradiction
swsh: maybe try eq-binop axiom
MorningScifi: 1 == 0 is false, boom Fields Medal
amratesh: @morningscifi lol no! not that simple
imaginenation: Man I would love to see some graphics programming over here :p
puffnfresh: in Agda and Idris I would use a dependent pattern match to prove "0 = 1 -> Void"
amratesh: YES
MorningScifi: @amratesh We can share the Fields Medal together, shhh don't tell the committee we cheated.
stale2000: 5Head
st47ik: try them all SMOrc
amratesh: there's the aha moment
imaginenation: This is too much mental gymnastics
imaginenation: you gotta focus, who does that I'm Pepega
lopm46: call of duty twitch channel got hacked this fuckien weird
imaginenation: ooh really?
eduardoadf1: he's triggering the third yee
eduardoadf1: eye'
eduardoadf1: monkaS
ensareray99: @georgehotz hey man what do you think about augmented realty ? I want to start a project about it. Do you think this tech has future or it will evolve something else?
imaginenation: I thought the purpose of life was to get hot girls and money
voodoorama: do you drink alcohol?
swsh: how about prove it on paper first?
eduardoadf1: modus ponens!
Thomasbrah: what is he making ?
BambiPT: 0 : 1
MorningScifi: Assume 1 = 0. If 1 = 0, then anything*0 = itself.
st47ik: @ensareray99 i think augmented reality combined with machine learning is the future but when exactly it will blow up idk
imaginenation: isn't Math actually metamath in the first place?
VinDanielYT: Hey
imaginenation: can you increase FONT please
imaginenation: size
amratesh: start by assuming 0=1. then 1=1. hence 0==1
xrealyy: you always put your 2 fingers on 4head while thinking @geohotz?
imaginenation: I cant see what he is typing
st47ik: activating the third eye to focus 4Head
imaginenation: @georgehotz font.size please :D
voodoorama: @imaginenation it's a secret
ensareray99: @st47ik Yeah it can be but right now the glasses is so annoying and hard to use. I dont know maybe with quantum computing it can be easier in the future and we can make better glasses
macca_r6: how do you find programming on a mac compared to a windows machine? @georgehotz
yoyo_brobro: yoyo_brobro subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 7 months, currently on a 7 month streak! legend
hexicity1: what is he coding?
c9bd: some shitty math proof i think
imaginenation: its funny that george complaints about views but doesnt have his stream alerts setup xD
amratesh: start with 0=1, then 1=1. then set theory (Parnetos principle) that a set cannot contain itself. hence 0==1
st47ik: no stream subscriber alerts NotLikeThis
imaginenation: exactly same with instagram, he wasnt even posting :(
imaginenation: I dont want my 7 month sub in a row to go unnoticed lol
xrealyy: is this even proofable?
imaginenation: FeelsBadMan
amratesh: dude read my previous message. yes I'm telling you to do stuff and I know you hate it
mrmusicmaine: there are few philosopher kings in tech, geohot it one of them
imaginenation: yeah but if he played by the rules of the attention economy he would be a billionaire by now
macca_r6: does he even read the chat lmao
imaginenation: which I dont get, why he doesnt want to go on joe roegan
imaginenation: exactly he doesnt even read whaty we are saying most of the time
amratesh: because it's drugs and mainstream press
st47ik: he went on Lex Fridman, was cool
imaginenation: we are just bots :( I was subbed to him 3 months in a row.
imaginenation: I loved his interview on lex for sure and his talk on breaking the simulation
macca_r6: he is a smart man. He is too busy to read the chat lmao
st47ik: MaN is focus is intense too
imaginenation: and thus he shouldnt complaint about not getting views
xxdvxx: reverse engineering math
imaginenation: or subs
amratesh: GEORGE!!!
amratesh: Start with 0=1.
SA20Knightmarre: hi george u look pretty today
amratesh: then Parneto got your back
imaginenation: @amratesh you're typign in vain my dude
amratesh: A set cannot contain itself
st47ik: :o
tsAllySparkles: start rapping again
imaginenation: i'm only interested in his comma ai stuff and other things I really dont enjoy this meta math stuff but oh well
lidermaury: Do u guys don't see code too?
imaginenation: yup too small
amratesh: lol you don't even know what's up
amratesh: comma ai is yes. but this is important
imaginenation: are you talking to me @amratesh ?
imaginenation: important to who?
imaginenation: exactly?
Zealeigh: I think Georges 'turbo' button is between his eyes? He keeps pushing it.
tsAllySparkles: what are you creating?
lidermaury: zoom in code
amratesh: let's just say important for the progression of humanity
st47ik: quick maths Kappa
imaginenation: @amratesh bruh look at this dood
zoki_macola: I watch him to learn something, but he doesnt like explaining himself to newbies
imaginenation: nah
amratesh: He doesn't want to be a streamed FFS. he goota do it. because that's what needs to be done rn
imaginenation: you dont learn jackshit by watching this stream lol
SA20Knightmarre: what time is it in california ?
amratesh: GEORGE A SET CANNOT CONTAIN ITSELF!
broadhawk: what about 1 1
imaginenation: this isnt a a learning stream, its watching geo go Pepega
st47ik: @SA20Knightmarre its on the top right lol 1:47 PM
imaginenation: lmao
imaginenation: @amratesh dude you're trying too hard and its making you look bad
cam_______: forkbomb(); forkbomb <---- will crash a unix operating system
st47ik: a set cannot contain itself SMOrc
xxdvxx: ok @cam_______
amratesh: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell's_paradox
st47ik: milk will make even more acid :s
st47ik: a set cannot contain itself NotLikeThis
SnakeAz: i love internet, you can watch and talk to one of the most influental hacker in the world, on my phone in my bed from africa.:)
amratesh: geohot can you gift me a subscription when my current one ends? lol
lidermaury: yes
amratesh: last text. sorry
C4TFive: I can be a doctor from webMD alone
th3_maj0r: hey hey
SnakeAz: best invention ever.
BambiPT: True
komocode_: is Elon still on track for robotaxis by end of next year?
st47ik: WebMD LUL
cam_______: The problem is the internet is also the biggest distraction that humans have ever had access to
st47ik: true
alexdickson98: @georgehotz what would be your advice to dedicate more time to programming and love it as much as you do
zoki_macola: Elon is always overpromising, dont listen to him
W1lkins: alexdickson98 are you srsly asking how to love something as much as someone else does bruh
Merwanedr: Glad to see he's back to Vim
BambiPT: still waiting cat girls from elon
lazystoic: can someone explain to a mortal what he is doing/trying to do?
cam_______: The Elon circlejerk is stupid
fwef64: Is George no longer using vscode?
Inconnu_xD: kuruF
st47ik: @alexdickson98 i think u have to grow ur interest to make it motivating first, and then try and do small milestones for rewards to keep you going
komocode_: is Tesla/Elon talk not allowed in here?
lidermaury: can you turn up the font size please
revolutionist123: monkaS
alexdickson98: @W1lkins i know its wierd but maybe he has some way of thinking that may change me
Merwanedr: It's a lot more inspiring when he uses Vim TMUX
smurfd0: "ice ice baby" :)
st47ik: Banana time Kreygasm
Merwanedr: I thought you were done with Metamath
alexdickson98: @st47ik thx, ill try the milestones/goals will see
swsh: maybe you should do it in scope $$, with $e wff = x 0 $ inside or something
amratesh: start with assuming 0=1. then prove 1=1. and then set theory
zoki_macola: But i think the robotaxis will be the first example of (almost) perfect tech, self sustaining in almost every way
alexdickson98: whats you rmath background
itsChoudhry: Math or metamath?
st47ik: Pure math is love
lazystoic: why arent we talking about selfdriving on this stream?
Merwanedr: Can you please stream programming related to cryptocurrencies in the future George? I've been waiting for a while since the BCH transaction stream haha
EpicDreamGod: are you trying to achieve enlightenment by giving yourself a brain freeze?
amratesh: we're only allowed to say comma ai is yes
chocolatechp: i learned how to give myself a haircut, do you want me to give you one
st47ik: amratesh is yes
Kyoto_o: nothing
alexdickson98: nothing haha
nautzz: monkaS
lidermaury: rip amratesh
komocode_: how come you don't use duck duck go?
xxdvxx: rip lol
amratesh: NOOO!
swsh: witness the history lol
Kyoto_o: that's why i'm not a sub, suck a dick LUL
amratesh: you can but don't
dontbeameme: Did u see the fight George ?
quevlo: what's your math background?
chocolatechp: chocolatechp subscribed with Twitch Prime.
amratesh: I'll shut up
FargioFarmani: drama right here
lazystoic: @komocode_ he doesnt really know programming, hes faking it
benpeterscode: everybody take it easy lol
dontbeameme: Fake programmer
st47ik: chat calm down NotLikeThis
zoki_macola: PogChamp
benpeterscode: make code not war haha
dontbeameme: Buffer overflow shell
Merwanedr: while he's not here
Merwanedr: any idea why George is mean to his subs?
SupaDeviserr: @dontbeameme wat does that mean?
xxdvxx: lets talk about self xrivi
Merwanedr: oops
dontbeameme: @supadeviserr I don’t know 🤷🏽♀️
amratesh: he's not mean. I was being silly
st47ik: he's not mean he just dont want to talk about those stuff
chocolatechp: do you have any emojis george
komocode_: what happened to his gaming PC?
matthewmirman: @georgehotz Twelf/LF is much more relevant to designing programs that reason about programs than metamath is, and much easier to write an automated theorem prover/verifier for you know
alexdickson98: this chat is useless no one helping
smurfd0: standupmaths on youtube is quite entertaining and dumbs down some math stuff.. would have loved to have him as a math teacher
lazystoic: @georgehotz what do u do for a living?
amratesh: Twelf/LF
st47ik: @alexdickson98 what do you need help with?
dontbeameme: @alexdickson98 I’m here as a HYPEMAN
alexdickson98: no i mean george ahhaha
SupaDeviserr: lately i've been enjoying vim buffers, i feel like ultra geek nerd now
komocode_: here's a math thing: twitch weird chat = subscriber only chat
lazystoic: this is like watching the matrix bro
dontbeameme: @komocode_ Sounds not very inclusive
TheKnopex: hows the cloud?
lazystoic: 1 1=2 ure welcome
amratesh: @lazystoic word
fwef64: fwef64 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
snowbola: are we trying to get george verified on instagram yet?
3even: Dude, nightmode your search results
3even: stylish plugin
amratesh: I don't want to annoy you anymore. but please read Russel's Paradox
3even: hahaha
lazystoic: @georgehotz whats ur iq bro
Yemtex: 5Head
st47ik: stylus extension for chrome? its open source
dontbeameme: George could just call up a homie but stubbornly wants to solve it on his own
3even: Yes Stylus. THats what i meant
3even: Extension for Chrome or FF
Merwanedr: Yo George has Metamask installed, what do you think he does with it?
amratesh: good night GeoHot. I gtg now
st47ik: good night @amratesh
fwef64: @georgehotz I've seen you use Emacs and VSCode on the stream, what makes you stick with good old Vim?
dontbeameme: Duckduckgo>google
st47ik: have u tried Twelf LF framework?
amratesh: Russell's paradox
bassxzero: Have you tried setting chat to wombo?
amratesh: You're literally stuck on Russel's Paradox. and you won't listen to me
meliodasfxk: is he using atom ?
amratesh: now bye. you can ban me but don't be calling me low quality FFS
montecarlo: no look at the top left
amratesh: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell's_paradox
xxdvxx: go sleep @amratesh
meliodasfxk: LUL
knight69gamer: monkaS
drShackle: LUL
dontbeameme: Lolololololol
dontbeameme: Lololololololo
st47ik: damn
smakatak: LUL
supnerdstv: does he rly know it
amratesh: Take a set
amratesh: it cannot contain a set
FargioFarmani: drama right here and now
lazystoic: hes right
amratesh: I'm sorry you can punish me :(
st47ik: LUL
meliodasfxk: LUL LUL
swsh: LUL
zoki_macola: im sweating
dontbeameme: Lololol
Richardable: SeemsGood SeemsGood
smakatak: BANNED
W1lkins: take a number 0, it cannot contain the number 1
alexdickson98: what switches do you use! @georgehotz
Merwanedr: ouch
rudolphdoesgames: gotta try that in my next math test
swsh: 0 is a black pixel, there math is broken confirmed
st47ik: @alexdickson98 check the bio :s
xrealyy: why do you even care about this meta math?
kzonixcomua: when do you plan to make leetcode (or hackerrank) stream?
alexdickson98: fuck
kzonixcomua: Or you do not
smakatak: am I the only one who doesn't know what geo actually doing
Merwanedr: Absolutely not.
xrealyy: nope
dontbeameme: Nope, low quality chat today
supnerdstv: isnt it obvious? Kappa
ortiga88: how to raise a permanent environment variable in linux from a service
ortiga88: ?
amratesh: I'm sorry. I'll be quite like I used to be
Merwanedr: I miss the time when he was streaming Bitcoin Cash transaction on Adderall.
meliodasfxk: what type of code editor is he using ? LUL
3even: Who was streaming Bitcoin Cash transactions on Adderall?
yuptheladsdownthecans: @meliodasfxk vi or vim maybe? Not sure
Merwanedr: George haha
foxubu: I miss the deep learning times (e.g., chess engine)
3even: @Merwanedr lol
meliodasfxk: @yuptheladsdownthecans ohh ok, ty :P
xrealyy: twitchess was nuts, still no idea what code mean but it was great anyway :D
eaterenrgy: I miss the capture the flag times.
Merwanedr: He even got into a controversy by saying that BCH is the real Bitcoin (for trolling)
The_Tyrant: george is there an email to contact you man?
Kriplok: Basic programming category on twitch, reading Russel's paradox. Good luck man)
3even: BCH IS the REAL Bitcoin
rudolphdoesgames: Where do you even get your ideas from?
th3_maj0r: I miss Great Pico CTF times
Lugueiro: @3even ?
MeGiveYouDie: ?use you do keyboard What
Merwanedr: I would rather say the original vision @3even
The_Tyrant: !setup
3even: Yes the P2P currency version
foxubu: I miss George ordering food
Merwanedr: Reality is subjective as people elect what they want in consensus algorithms (PoW)
3even: I miss George's lady friend
Merwanedr: I MISS GEORGE MAKING FOOD @foxubu
kzonixcomua: What he is doing is a basic programing in 2019 - evolution baby =)
lucasmaekawa: what book is this?
zigzati: @lucasmaekawa metamath
foxubu: The Metamath book I guess
lucasmaekawa: ty guys
xrealyy: anyone waiting for Musk's cybertruck?
xxdvxx: we dont talk musk here
matthewmirman: https://gist.github.com/mmirman/0bb05b2736c35d4278c7f8d9888d9af4
xxdvxx: we're math stream now
foxubu: Elon left Twitter :D
matthewmirman: ^^ 2 2=4 in 5 min
matthewmirman: in twelf
xDestris: can someone explain me what is he doing
lidermaury: Geo the type of bygga to fart into the toilet and flush
dontbeameme: Didn’t wash hands
litenull: wash your hands bro
peter35_: are we using peano arithmetic?
dontbeameme: Eating nails didn’t wash hands
3even: @lidermaury lol
matthewmirman: pretty chill
smurfd0: im starting to understand why math people in the past tried to drill a hole in the skull to improve thinking capabillities :]
swsh: you signed up for this when you dropped coq for a more hacker version
matthewmirman: you don't need nat to be anything special
matthewmirman: you should define it all
matthewmirman: yeah its poorly designed
matthewmirman: we had to do all that in a very similar thing to metamath in math logic at cmu
matthewmirman: it was hell
dontbeameme: Is this basically a crossword for smart people
zigzati: @dontbeameme crossword doesnt use your brain tho
zigzati: just recalling stuff
cybermajestic: george helloo
dontbeameme: @zigzati Yes , problem solving
swsh: first prove 0 != 1, don't bother with plus
matthewmirman: I think, without knowing too many of the details of metamath, is that you end up defining naturals using actual peano arithmetic which is a low level instantiation of induction and not the higher order abstractions over induction that better designed languages have
matthewmirman: it'd likely be even easier in agda/idris
metis_zver: Hello, how do you save your eyes?
matthewmirman: I think though CoQ and Agda have the issue that code (equality checking) isn't something you can prove things about
matthewmirman: whereas in Twelf/LF, your code (plus, equality checking) is actually something you can prove things about, not just a definition
jesuuusete: what language is he writing ?
matthewmirman: currently CoQ, before metamath
parviz_a4: hi
sutures_md: Have you used OCaml @georgehotz ? Pretty rich type-system and some sweet compilers to play around with
decarbonite: is this lisp NotLikeThis
matthewmirman: yo also, I'd recommend agda over CoQ, fewer random keywords to remember
matthewmirman: its less mathy sure
MacoNighto: my teachers made coq and ocaml
matthewmirman: but thats kinda the point
Plurmorant: Lean BabyRage
MacoNighto: if anyone cares
st47ik: how about Twelf?
st47ik: u tried it?
matthewmirman: if your in a proving math mindset, its a lot harder to understand how automated theorem verifiers actually work and how to prove things with them
MacoNighto: what's cool with coq it's that they made compcert, a mathematically proven C compiler
matthewmirman: the axioms are derivable
matthewmirman: (or at least a lot are)
sirleeroyjenkins: How u doin George hope everythings going well
matthewmirman: from a smaller core of axioms
matthewmirman: like for example axiom of choice
matthewmirman: you can prove axiom of choice from nothing in CoQ/Agda
sutures_md: anyone else here in Boston?
MacoNighto: do you know why they named it coq ?
MacoNighto: c'est le seul animal qui arrive à chanter les pieds dans la merde
amratesh: 👀
MacoNighto: MacoNighto subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Richardable: le coq sportif
MacoNighto: haha
matthewmirman: yes
st47ik: LUL
bankzed: Hello from IRC
xDestris: monkaS
matthewmirman: the thing with the proof in twelf, is that you can prove something about the proof itself also when your done
matthewmirman: which is what you eventually want to be doing I assume
nanodanger7: nanodanger7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 18 months, currently on a 18 month streak! 18
matthewmirman: the problem in CoQ is that you end up in prop
matthewmirman: and once your at the bottom level you can't go down more
matthewmirman: kinda, idris has the best solution for it: it topologically sorts your theorems
matthewmirman: and you never have to worry about it
matthewmirman: everything is just "type"
matthewmirman: but there, you don't have to think about it
matthewmirman: not russell's paradox
shieeeeeeeeet: are you going to switch to a statically typed language for your interpreter?
matthewmirman: its a different paradox
matthewmirman: omega paradox
matthewmirman: way harder to understand
swsh: LUL LUL
amratesh: 👀
zoki_macola: lol
st47ik: @amratesh u still here LUL
matthewmirman: the type theory version
matthewmirman: I'll find a link to the agda proof of it somewhere
P3droPL: @georgehotz Why you came back to Mac? What is wrong with Razer Win?
xrealyy: pedro co my tu robimy, ten goscto jakis swir
BryanSWAGBEAST: yo what's up George! long time no see
P3droPL: haha
matthewmirman: called girard's paradox for type theory
matthewmirman: russels paradox and girards paradox have non isomorphic proofs
superman03: hi
matthewmirman: https://github.com/nzl-nott/PhD-of-nzl/blob/master/Exercise/Ex4/girard.agda
Celestial_Jaeger: what do you do for a living george
C4TFive: New things DansGame DansGame DansGame DansGame
K177Music: Hi, I'm here to ask about your keyboard :)
K177Music: what keyboard do you use :)
itsChoudhry: LOL ^
matthewmirman: I guess yeah, typically learning about all the ways you shouldn't do something helps you learn the right way to do it
nautzz: wouldnt it be good to just mute everyone other than matthewmirman in the chat
nautzz: everything else is just noise
C4TFive: We should all stop talking for @matthewmirman
K177Music: i think george is an engineer of some sorts
superman03: do you know what's going on with libratus?
Celestial_Jaeger: i just wanted to know how george earns money
xrealyy: who is this guy and why he's not working in comma ai
K177Music: fr, wheres my cheap autonomous vehciles 😡
C4TFive: This is heorge gotz
lidermaury: you guys have no idea what are you doing
K177Music: vehicles **
xrealyy: i like pickled onions
K177Music: same
BryanSWAGBEAST: I though Geroge was moving to Mixer lmao
K177Music: hes waiting for the $2m contract PepeLaugh
Celestial_Jaeger: also I like how the category of this is Basic Programming for a lack of a more appropriate sub category within programming, but this is anything else but Basic Programming
bankzed: Nah, he's coding his own streaming platform
C4TFive: hes gotta get that mixer money first
swsh: prove 1 = 1 from x = x
K177Music: I'm loving this basic programming you're doing
amratesh: 👁️
K177Music: hes doing a gang sign TriHard
K177Music: it means that x is equal to x
matthewmirman: typically you have an axiom of reflection
matthewmirman: but I don't see how that helps you with 1 != 0
BryanSWAGBEAST: Mac or Windows?
xrealyy: so axiom means something obviousness, certainty, got it
matthewmirman: not really
matthewmirman: axiom means something we've decided is fundamental
matthewmirman: it might not be obvious
cathandez: why not use Maple
cathandez: JK idk what im talking about
xrealyy: wow so there's no assurances that this is true, math has a lot of depth, i go back to shadow
rektiw0w: abstract mathematics monkaS
MrBankster: hey BrO!
NoLimitFitness: !uptime
SA20Knightmarre: what is the language ?
xrealyy: when i first heard word axiom in college i couldnt stand still
rektiw0w: @xrealyy gives me anxiety thinking abt it
matthewmirman: @xrealyy in fact if you try to prove logic is consistent you need to assume the existence of an ordinal not definable in that logic. if you assume all ordinals exist, you are inconsistent
NoLimitFitness: sub alerts set up?
matthewmirman: so provably, we can't prove anything works
SA20Knightmarre: @rektiw0w same, and my math professor often says "that is trivial" when it was so hard for me
johngeorgesample: johngeorgesample subscribed with Twitch Prime.
matthewmirman: see, the issue with proof search for stupid languages like metamath and peter andrew's thing (and first order logic proof systems) is that you basically can't narrow down the search at all intelligently by types, since the types are so simple
xrealyy: seems like you learn a lot matthew, congrats its hard these days
matthewmirman: there are infinite combinations of them
swsh: eureka
ZeeZaxean: Pog
xrealyy: clicked in the head
bloodborne24: we're learning bois PogChamp
matthewmirman: the issue with more intelligent languages with more complex types is that typically searches among them are intentionally designed by the programmer by default
smurfd0: search for "2 2=4" on that metamath page. you have some ideas on how to approac it (there is some trivia ... you proably read it)
matthewmirman: there isn't a language yet thats put together some way of learning tactics for complex types
swsh: so does tzero tsucc pa_ax1 works?
hughjohnson: keyboard?
superdorage: PorscheWIN
hughjohnson: MonkaS
matthewmirman: I have a couple ideas for how youd do this with problog style inference on top of a logic programming core version of PTS/idris (what I was building in caledon before apple)
wiseai: HELL YEAH :)
matthewmirman: i.e. learn problog
matthewmirman: well, probabilistic programming languages are shit at the moment
matthewmirman: https://github.com/mmirman/caledon
swsh: i've tried Pyro by uber, there are uses!
matthewmirman: probabalistic programming isn't the problem as much as the idea hasn't been developed enough
matthewmirman: its still in the "we have lambda calculus 1920" phase
matthewmirman: so problog (and now my team's psi) has this nice inference thing
matthewmirman: where you learn probabilities of facts
matthewmirman: if you get enough facts
matthewmirman: you have a neural network
matthewmirman: but thats useless
matthewmirman: in problog at least, because it would be hella inneficient
matthewmirman: and also there are no types
matthewmirman: so you can't then use your neural network to reason about programs
matthewmirman: or do any sort of search
amratesh: @matthewmirman I think I got it, gimme a minute I gotta check
matthewmirman: well the problem is to make them useful
swsh: saying there is no uses for PP is like saying statisticians do nothing, how about Stan, PyMC
matthewmirman: yeah, also, our team is like actively selling probabilistic programming languages to users
shieeeeeeeeet: how does proving program equality -> you can find bugs?
matthewmirman: at eth
matthewmirman: nah, psi
shieeeeeeeeet: or is it like finding bugs in diffs of the same codebase?
leander_ms: Hey, what is your typing WPM score @georgehotz
matthewmirman: https://github.com/eth-sri/psi
swsh: Probabilistic MetaMath PogChamp
swsh: let's prove 2 2 =4 with 95% confidence
baymer1: yo it's the LEGEND
protectionfromblue: vter
protectionfromblue: jk
superdorage: Can anyone calculate the probability of me being accepted from Y combinator batch?
MiniManiacBlob: @georgehotz g'day sir
baymer1: Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 Terminator1 bonus2 what if phi
veritasjs: hi
MiniManiacBlob: so whats the objective here?
superdorage: TheIlluminati
Vesh: evening george
bubblesnot: hey random question do you know anything about detecting polymorphic and metamorphic computer viruses?
yeah_haey: Can i hang out with you in la
yeah_haey: Why arent you using Grothendieck toposes
yeah_haey: Prove gauss bonnet theorem
eduardoadf1: prove metamath
The_Tyrant: george any email to contact you? please
matthewmirman: its after midnight here I'm out, if you get to actual neural proof search lmk
superdorage: @the_tyrant my autograph is available.
The_Tyrant: dowrigUK
Piqcyl: Hey Goerge, I'n a previous stream I watched on YouTube you took L-Theanine. Would you say it has actually cognitive benefits or is it a placebo?
Piqcyl: in*
amir_shehata: hey my man ur the best in python
andrewnakas: andrewnakas subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 2 month streak! Friick yes
andrewnakas: Oh Frick yah
amir_shehata: what is this project about
andrewnakas: its a coq
amir_shehata: and what language guys
andrewnakas: for backspace ai starter pack
andrewnakas: porting metamath to python
andrewnakas: python is language
amir_shehata: ty <3 <3 <3
swsh: PogChamp
roronoa_d_law: tf is he doing
amir_shehata: ru live now on yoytube
idkfa22: Big fan of your work
idkfa22: I think you are awesome
Piqcyl: hi youtube
alexdickson98: how does this man not get tired
Ace: @georgehotz you hiring?
cerrad1234: wtf is even going on
Piqcyl: @alexdickson98 how do you not get tired when you go about your day?
StupidGladiator: how can i become a great dev, im fed up with web development
alexdickson98: true
alexdickson98: xd
JesseSkinner: pchai
superdorage: Sundar pichai
Piqcyl: Math is a set of axioms and definitions, from this you can make deductions through rigorous proof. Pretty sure what he is building the mathematical framework to deal with these objects. Theoretically you can discover new mathematics through brute force and this is a possible future development in mathematics. Not sure why George is interested in it rn tho.
Artistxtv: ur smart as hell lol
swsh: your cam obscures some code >(
Piqcyl: Is phi a set?
amratesh: 👀
function_2win: liked the chat with Lex
SKPTCL: Long stream today
amratesh: I like it
Piqcyl: @georgehotz does L-Theanine actually have noticeable benefits?
SKPTCL: Nootropics are a meme piqcyl
Piqcyl: George took it in a previous stream
Piqcyl: Just wondering
Piqcyl: I'm aware of that, coffee doesnt make me smarter but it definitely helps me get things done.
amir_shehata: can i be billionaire from Programming PogChamp LUL LUL LUL
Piqcyl: If i buy coursera ML courses and take nootropics will i be a bitcoin billionaire data wizard?
Piqcyl: lmaoooo
Piqcyl: George why are you working on this? Out of interest or does it have relevance to your other projects?
smurfd0: write it in english first, then go from there?
zoki_macola: is there a programming language that consists of just a few simple rules and everything else is made through metaprogramming
Piqcyl: what is the notation x t
Piqcyl: x is an element of t?
Piqcyl: for all x, phi -> for all x, (x=t), implies phi. Not sure the syntax here but doesnt this mean you are implying that phi implies itself?
Piqcyl: yea this syntax is janky as hell lol
Super_saiyan_3: can anybody tell me what hes trying to do? lol
Piqcyl: computational framework for mathematical logic
Piqcyl: that what coq is
Super_saiyan_3: ah, sounds to complicated for me
jay_al97: are u still trying to understand metamath
Piqcyl: Are you doing this for pure interest?
Piqcyl: Or is it one step towards a larger project
zoki_macola: but I don't understand why are you trying to prove a thing. What does proving something has to do with creating complex data structures or whatever
Piqcyl: Theoretically if you are able to computationally represent mathematics and all of its axioms. You should be able to use computational power to brute force discover new TRUE mathematical statements.
snapcs1: theory is a big part of computer science
BigBrainDota: you guys are on some 200 iq shit
Piqcyl: try print(" 2 2 = 4")
SlaterUSA: what's the ritalin count today, boys? :D
SlaterUSA: 4:30 y0lo blazit
notmichael: GEOHOT WHATS GOOD SON
Piqcyl: http://us.metamath.org/mpegif/mmset.html#2p2e4length
Piqcyl: this website looks like it might be relevant
lazystoic: @georgehotz have you ever tried DMT?
smurfd0: https://www.math.wustl.edu/~kumar/courses/310-2011/Peano.pdf or maby https://www.cs.toronto.edu/~sacook/csc438h/notes/page96.pdf two fat pdfs .. not sure though
twiggy_io: Hello George
swsh: let's contact the author of peano.mm and ask him
twiggy_io: Im starting to think a lot of the internet is a waste of time.
Piqcyl: Why is that
andrewnakas: I do
dorkmo: ROBER LETSSS GOOO
notmichael: Yes yes
swsh: 80 years old daaamn
Piqcyl: https://math.berkeley.edu/~solovay/
Piqcyl: give him a call hahaha
etess9001: ResidentSleeper
dorkmo: oregon
dorkmo: doxing robert
zoki_macola: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_M._Solovay
dorkmo: x x = 4
Piqcyl: So what are you guys workin on
notmichael: Well
zoki_macola: Robert Solovay is a boomer
cutza: order a pizza
Piqcyl: George is a boomer
gunnaren: uber eats
notmichael: LUL
nautzz: fix u up some rice & bananas somali style
Piqcyl: Chicken Masala
Alandas99: !uptime
notmichael: You okay man? lol
notmichael: LOL
kungfudog2012: jasonrBangem
Piqcyl: Dang didnt get to read what he said
notmichael: Time to ring up robert
gunnaren: will you do any writeup of this when ur done?
swsh: hard stuff makes us better
twiggy_io: Metamath is pretty black and white.
Piqcyl: Why are you doing this? Is a step towards a larger goal or is this just pure interest?
Piqcyl: sorry for 2nd time asking lol
notmichael: I won't lie, I have no fricking clue what's going on. I'm just here cause george
64pillars: 5Head ah yes
gunnaren: @notmichael Half the job is pretending to know what's going on :D
maefff: bless you
notmichael: BLESS YOU
fear_ep: bless you
ADivorcedFork: 5Head
notmichael: Every move george makes is a 5Head move
Piqcyl: good luck m8
Piqcyl: gtg
thuganalyst: This is so complicated
TokaMakaridze: what are you doing man? WutFace WutFace
gunnaren: we gotta get your instagram to 20k by the end of the year
PrinceKingly: chat why is it a timeout if you ask him about his keyboard ? LUL
smurfd0: is this the set thing you are not looking for? https://math.stackexchange.com/questions/627434/prove-that-4-is-the-only-solution-to-22
itsChoudhry: For those who don't understand what is going on someone linked him metamath he started exploring it now he's trying to make it work. Metamath is good for verifying things by axioms you define. (I'm guessing form what I understand) There's no defined goal, apart from trying to work it out.
vave2_: so is this like a program that proves math theorems
itsChoudhry: from*
thuganalyst: @princekingly because that question gets asked A LOT so it probably got annoying. I think he should just put it in the stream description or something
thuganalyst: Or set up a bot to answer that question lol
PrinceKingly: maybe there's a bot for it let me check
PrinceKingly: !keyboard
PrinceKingly: no there isn't LUL
itsChoudhry: @vave2_ Yh basically
TeaLeafi: geo are u jewish?
TeaLeafi: the keyboarding clicking is soo ASMR.. <3
itsChoudhry: He should write a bot to timeout people who ask about the keyboard in chat. He could use this metamath to verify it works LUL
notmichael: Lol why are you asking if hes jewish xD
TeaLeafi: just curious
NotFire_: tealeaf is jewish KappaHD , jewish people like to ask other people if they are jewish. no particular reason, just cuz MiniK
notmichael: PogChamp
itsChoudhry: Fuck yeah
TeaLeafi: WutFace
fear_ep: are you an AI? KappaHD
PrinceKingly: guys can you buy the stuff he created to make your car drive itself
notmichael: Its on their website
notmichael: comma.ai
TeaLeafi: bet
notmichael: off
zoki_macola: NotLikeThis
NotFire_: @fear_ep i think you're on to him Kappa you got him spooked, we dont talk about that here Kappa
robby0313: Why meta math
TeaLeafi: "we dont talk about that here" in what regards???
NotFire_: @TeaLeafi him being an ai
NotFire_: AI
itsChoudhry: It's like fightclub SHHHHH
TeaLeafi: we dont talk about it truee..!
TeaLeafi: @NotFire_ arent we all just A.I's in the BIG universal server protocol?
NotFire_: @TeaLeafi No FUNgineer
TeaLeafi: each living being, or living carbon/silicon atom is a byte in memory of the program.
TeaLeafi: the universe is holographic simulation. #scaryFACTS
PrinceKingly: i'm watching this and to be honest i understand shit. just watching coz it's geo
notmichael: Same lol
smurfd0: the bytes must have been expensive when they thought of this language :D
TeaLeafi: when you can create matter out of nothing and ultiimate divine intelligence, you can create anything UwU
phrixus_bro: does he talk to himself when he programs for real or just on stream for our sake?
TeaLeafi: asburgers he talks to himself @phrixus_bro
AHIOV: Most likely both
notmichael: asburgers? lmao
NotFire_: both
NotFire_: but mostly for us
phrixus_bro: cool
AHIOV: Is Hackintosh worth the hassle just for the sake of having 2 different OS ?
TeaLeafi: @AHIOV no just Linux
notmichael: If you really need windows and macos then sure it is lol
TeaLeafi: @AHIOV kali linux so u can do some gangsh1t
notmichael: kali linux so you can do some gang gang hacker shiz naw mean?
TeaLeafi: i mean ur not wrong
AHIOV: LUL LUL I'll think about it
amzirK: hello my dude
josalt: Hey everyone
notmichael: hi
amzirK: @josalt HeyGuys
TeaLeafi: UwU
notmichael: Something happened!
zipppyzoom: SeemsGood1 SeemsGood1 SeemsGood1 SeemsGood1 SeemsGood1
swsh: commit push
anokhiml: this is proof verification?
cod4TV: do hackthebox!
TeaLeafi: good job!
cod4TV: PLZ, do hackthebox!
TeaLeafi: hackthebox!
gunnaren: weird question, but; Is this more of a programming challenge or a math challenge?
TeaLeafi: this is a chemistry challenge @gunnaren
anokhiml: lol
andrewnakas: its a basic programming challgenge
gunnaren: I miss subonly chat
TeaLeafi: Geo did u get "Death Stranding" game?
cod4TV: How is this categorized as "Basic Programming"?
th3_maj0r: @gunnaren lol
cod4TV: It's really Advanced!
gunnaren: @th3_maj0r Don't you agree :D ?
TeaLeafi: this is childs play lol @cod4TV
th3_maj0r: maybe
anokhiml: hes learning the language though so... basic
peter35_: i recently heard of curry-howard-lambek as well; adding in cat theory
Cicero4259: cs major with math minor vs math major vs cs minor? @georgehotz (I wanna do ml with just a bs)
anokhiml: cs major, statistics major
briva56: briva56 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
grizvok: yeah stats would probably be better if you truly want to just go into ml
anokhiml: really it would be math major with extra stats classes
dorkmo: this mustache https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/W._Hugh_Woodin
cod4TV: Get back to hacking!
hazrid93: wetf is metamath
TeaLeafi: how about just self learning...? no need for some dumb fancy paper to proof that you know how to do it! @peter35_ @Cicero4259 @anokhiml
th3_maj0r: @cod4TV I think the timeout from George is really close dude
dorkmo: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ω-logic
M0tyak: Should i learn vi ?
cod4TV: @th3_maj0r Indeed! BibleThump
zakonegrusha: hacking is super boring
bubblesnot: what are you proving here?
TeaLeafi: CHIK FILET?
anokhiml: @TeaLeafi he asked which degree is better lol
zakonegrusha: 0 is equal to 1
TeaLeafi: POPEYUES
bubblesnot: define 1 and define 0
TeaLeafi: POPEYES CHICKEN SANDWHICH??
cod4TV: No, this is boring, hacking is more fun!
zakonegrusha: If 1-0 = 0, then 0 - 1 would equal -0? hah gotcha
TeaLeafi: @cod4TV shhhhhhh
zakonegrusha: @cod4TV your wrong, HTB and hacking sucks
TeaLeafi: hacking is boring...
zakonegrusha: legit a bunch of nerds
zakonegrusha: thinking that MSF is cool
TeaLeafi: omg geo saw my chat <3 <3 <3 <3 FANGIRLING <3 <#
cod4TV: the fontconfig stream was awesome!
cod4TV: that's what i call hacking!
cod4TV: why?
zakonegrusha: bunch of skids.
cod4TV: @doganigooo2 yes
cod4TV: who's the moderator?
th3_maj0r: Don't talk about commaai guys, he will timeout yoou
revolutionist123: anyone know how he exits incert mode on vim
revolutionist123: *insert
th3_maj0r: by pressing ESC?
jax05_: lookup vim cheat sheets
revolutionist123: cause many people bind it to another key
jax05_: I see
cod4TV: how many min is the TO?
th3_maj0r: Check his vimrc, btw I don't think he rebinded it
coProof: POGGERS
Ammari1: Hey I am a big fan, did you hear of CheckRa1n? Would be nice going through an explanation of how the exploit works
coProof: i never understand how were really ever doing anything in these twitchcoqs
cod4TV: he ignores chat
Ammari1: Does he read chat?
jax05_: not really, he's just thinking
jax05_: he reads chat
doganigooo2: yea he reads got TO twice
cod4TV: lol!
JustAnEdtior: did u get to prove that true is not false?
coProof: ill be back later
cod4TV: geo, can i live the glory of TO?
cod4TV: HKKB Pro 2 LOL!
cod4TV: HHKB*
cod4TV: COMMA AI is the best
cod4TV: Do hacking!
cod4TV: You are hungry don't code!
cod4TV: HAPPY HACKING KEYBOARD doo doo doo doo
th3_maj0r: Was that a real question?? ahahah
cod4TV: aren't u hungry ? eat first than you can keep coding
cod4TV: Police are coming to you, geo
altic: !uptime
zoki_macola: is that a dog howling
cod4TV: I am anti-TO
th3_maj0r: 4h 52 minutes
cod4TV: B|
cod4TV: is it geo or george?
Scott_w_c: "basic programming"
skate77777: I love u dude
skate77777: And im sick of you cod4TV
cod4TV: @Scott_w_c Very Basic!
Scott_w_c: lambda calculus = simple stuff
Scott_w_c: i wanna know how this dude did in highschool
Scott_w_c: probs better than most teachers
dawgwhisper007: ignore it = ignorant
cod4TV: @skate77777 STFU!
skate77777: You talk too much dont you think?
skate77777: And you Forgot to tell him to eat something
cod4TV: @skate77777 That what chat for my friend..
isensualism: Hey @georgehotz have you ever done any devirtualization? Any resources you can point to? I'm quite comfortable with unpacking, but stuck on devirtualization.
isensualism: something like Themida running code through a VM
isensualism: :^)
QuantumComputingMIT: Suh
QuantumComputingMIT: Aggressive typing
jax05_: progress
erichtp: Terminator15 bonus1
dorkmo: Party1
QuantumComputingMIT: Axiomatically axiomatic
foogs_: I don't even understand normal people words :(
QuantumComputingMIT: Layman of laymens
QuantumComputingMIT: Is this prerecorded
OhDyrHesUdyr: idk
thundershots999: This is live
QuantumComputingMIT: Can't tell, no interaction
shieeeeeeeeet: let the man think
pouringhotteaonyourface: !project
QuantumComputingMIT: He's been thinking for a while
th3_maj0r: It's live, he will answer you if you ask something smart
andrewnakas: geo Hotz you a legend
QuantumComputingMIT: Maybe you predicted that name
raidbossxxx: what
QuantumComputingMIT: hax0r the future
QuantumComputingMIT: @georgehotz Can I work for you for free
phrixus_bro: i like the floors of the apartment
searchingforlife: visual studio looks so different now @georgehotz
foogs_: i just wanna be here when he finds something to exploit the simulation
pouringhotteaonyourface: why did he choose mm rather than
andrewnakas: Hotz im curious what the steps you envision it takes to go from metamath coq prover thing to programming agent from a high level
gordopeIotudo: do you think P=NP?
QuantumComputingMIT: What is this trash language
QuantumComputingMIT: metamath?
QuantumComputingMIT: How long did it take you to learn it
QuantumComputingMIT: And what is your end goal
th3_maj0r: Trash language? you mean java?
QuantumComputingMIT: Java is also trash
QuantumComputingMIT: JavaScript on the other hand
th3_maj0r: also thrash
th3_maj0r: trash**
EEsmash: I like html Kappa
TrapperMx: Kappa
QuantumComputingMIT: ban ur mod
QuantumComputingMIT: he said javascript is trash
CopyNine: D:
SKPTCL: Wasn’t me don’t ban me pls
QuantumComputingMIT: wtf
andrewnakas: lol
th3_maj0r: get rekt!
QuantumComputingMIT: What is ur fav then
andrewnakas: python
th3_maj0r: I like goland
QuantumComputingMIT: Python is for beta males
dorkmo: need some mochi ice cream
QuantumComputingMIT: Malbolge #1
Mbsurfer: What keyboard are you using? Sounds topre. HHKB?
slowgonzales: guys best idea is learn every language and go with which u liked most :D
QuantumComputingMIT: @Mbsurfer ask about keyboard = timeout
Mbsurfer: Just read that in the description. The one thing lol my bad
alextodoroki: @georgehotz i think about you nightly before i go to bed and daily when i wake up. i have a shrine of you that is encrusted and i want to have your babies.
QuantumComputingMIT: wtf
DiaLab: Why is he using terminal for a text editor?
andrewnakas: its vim
QuantumComputingMIT: iOS
QuantumComputingMIT: lol
andrewnakas: @alextodoroki then where is the sub lol?
alextodoroki: do i look like i have a million dollars sir
QuantumComputingMIT: Can someone explain what he's doing?
mirceau: Hi George, I am going to switch from Thinkpad to Macbook. What is your CPU/RAM ?
thundershots999: This is a rice stream with some basic programming
th3_maj0r: @mirceau He don't really like to talk about hardware
mirceau: @th3_maj0r oh.. I that he was a tech guys
mirceau: thought*
QuantumComputingMIT: He is...
th3_maj0r: anyway, take the best for your budget and you are gonna be fine
th3_maj0r: more like a math guy
QuantumComputingMIT: math guy?
mirceau: haha math guy indeed :)
QuantumComputingMIT: more like logic guy
th3_maj0r: Mod said math guy!
dorkmo: please dont label people
QuantumComputingMIT: Yes sir!
mirceau: match aids logic
mirceau: math*
QuantumComputingMIT: He's math fluid
gtnftw: can someone tell me what he is trying to do rn?
th3_maj0r: math stream from a math guy
MrMarkFilaroski: coding for dollars again?
QuantumComputingMIT: put ur head closer to the cam
MrMarkFilaroski: can you see me now? @QuantumComputingMIT
MrMarkFilaroski: Kappa LUL chesscomBrilliant
gtnftw: can you briefly go over what you're doing rn for any people who just joined(me)
guy_ross: guy_ross is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to zoki_macola!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to erichtp!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to euranymous!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to lemonboxed!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to Mendacii_!
guy_ross: howdy
thundershots999: Hello
erichtp: thanks for the gifted sub homie @guy_ross
guy_ross: np
jbyte1988: for me
Mariosavitch: is this over your head
jbyte1988: my suscribsion
SKPTCL: Thanks guy ross
IWasnotDemi: What is george doing?
andrewnakas: 0 != 1
andrewnakas: proofing that
mortalog: hey am new to this what u doing ?
Knarez: wtf is this language LUL
WalnutsRule: whats your favorite compiler
vsudo: have you checked out checkra1n
Doodle_Jump92: I dont think so
zeroeagle1: hello everyone
mortalog: okey i went to metamath home page and i guess i found my new addiction
zeroeagle1: Cheer900
katangeu: is that a ysl hoodie lmao I have the same one I think
stupac62: Chat: new here. Is he doing this stuff for intellectual stimulation? Or is there a different goal?
flopagis: @stupac62 his ai is going to use his own version of math itself
zeroeagle1: when he's doing $(...)$ is it creating an atom or something?
stupac62: @flopagis ah interesting. Thanks!
smurfd0: no $ is comments
zeroeagle1: oh right I see
flopagis: @stupac62 im joking i have no idea
stupac62: @flopagis come on. I was starting to google to figure out what the heck that meant
zeroeagle1: learn something practically useless to learn something new
flopagis: @stupac62 haha sorry. if you are interested you could look up alternatives to Euclidean geometry etc
andrewnakas: bye
andrewnakas: u a legend
samtheprogram: !uptime
th3_maj0r: @georgehotz Host someone from "basic programming"
gajuun: this makes me so happy that someone is streaming programming.
stupac62: What will you call the wrapper around coq?
MrOtotheP: @georgehotz I understand the choice, but why not go with metamath zero or lean? (judging by your frustration)
smurfd0: rofl
zeroeagle1: maby can check on git matching file extension for examples?
MrOtotheP: I feel like Lean has the advantage of also being JUST a programming language..
zeroeagle1: must have been written by schoolars
th3_maj0r: host someone
zeroeagle1: cya take care
th3_maj0r: byeee
SKPTCL: Take care m8
samtheprogram: tyty take care
ET_515: ah man I just got here
knilecrack: Wsup
drivewaycam: george
KyleUE: yeet
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: meow
drivewaycam: holiday
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: shoutouts comma ai archive
snxraven: HEYYY
kornez: yo
zoki_macola: my ears
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: comedyStare comedyStare comedyStare
vbhv: yooo gehot
drivewaycam: modGeeTron modGeeTron modGeeTron
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz comedyStare comedyStare comedyStare comedyStare comedyStare comedyStare comedyStare
beefydangles: feelin hot.hot.hot
bebytesback: YO!
haircutjimmy: hullooo
ekalsuwaidi: LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: LUL
kornez: @i4cc8a9morw8kfrh mizkifYo
MacS7n: Good morning
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @kornez comedyStare
MorningScifi: Today we prove 1 = 2? Aw shit
itsxaos: @georgehotz i just started catching up on the twitchcoq vods and just wanted to say youre the best
drivewaycam: i love search
harmanthebest1: nubbinToddler
vbhv: ever been to India?
forkdb: Hello george
drivewaycam: i love india
phrixus_bro: indian food
rawfael: hello from Brazil
Joemerlino: I just bought a white panda but didn’t know chffr was discontinued in the meanwhile :(
alexdickson98: how are you today george
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: yes, very simple 5Head
haircutjimmy: I need to see pep8 today @georgehotz
bebytesback: was your talk from UCSD recorded?
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: jonesy5SillyChamp jonesy5SillyChamp
keepingtrckofthisacct: yo
Azizerinotv: yo
Azizerinotv: !project
marsroger44: whats up boys
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @neptun44 comedyStare
Baldaz_: metamaths??
alexdickson98: what's your opinion on ruby? @georgehotz
marsroger44: geohot back on twitch #vibeesss
titifodidi: You know someone is for real when they use vim this quick
keepingtrckofthisacct: @alexdickson98 don't do it...:D
sausainismilka: @georgehotz sup george. good luck SeemsGood
Baldaz_: difference between forward and backward search???
marsroger44: whtat happened to coq? did he gave up on it
smurfd0: great, progress :)
alexdickson98: @keepingtrckofthisacct wdym
dimplik: @georgehotz when you going quantum computing?
railander: @titifodidi PogChamp
keepingtrckofthisacct: @alexdickson98 you'll see
burimbushii: for what can this program used ??
titifodidi: 🤯
Baldaz_: Hey @georgehotz what's the difference between forward and backward search???
MacS7n: I'm kinda lost. recap ? please don't ban me
gigafact: was about to upload the part4 but looks like I am going to upload both part4&part5 combined...
euranymous: George can you give us the link for the repo?
alexdickson98: @georgehotz have you every thought about creating a probraming language?
bebytesback: @georgehotz was your talk from UCSD recorded?
ZeeZaxean: wth george is becoming an everyday streamer? where is the schedule? Kappa
brisingr1031: @euranymous https://github com/geohot/twitchcoq
euranymous: Thanks
keepingtrckofthisacct: @alexdickson98 he's kinda doing that now
brisingr1031: @georgehotz thoughts on tmux vs gnu screen
phrixus_bro: ok
marsroger44: saint laurent in the house
Baldaz_: so foward = general, backward = specific search, that it??
Huskieee: all you need in life is nano
railander: LUL
xrealyy: almost 8 am and coding? he's mad
UzeezU: fuck yeah backwards search
alexdickson98: @keepingtrckofthisacct haha ok
keepingtrckofthisacct: @alexdickson98 here it comes
keepingtrckofthisacct: lol
alexdickson98: noo
railander: no pls monkaS
puffnfresh: yes
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz comedyStare
dotmops: wesbtwMonka
ekalsuwaidi: @i4cc8a9morw8kfrh Wrap it up domer squadD
matthewmirman: Does metamath have classical inference rules, or are you working with a set of axioms that includes double negation elimination or something?
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @ekalsuwaidi ok dude comedyOkay
ekalsuwaidi: This is some 5Head shit i dont even know why im here :)
marsroger44: do you think hackintoshing is secure in terms of file integrity?
dotmops: wrap it up mathey
doganigooo2: let me remind you the rules ... 1-do not ask anything about that ai thing 2-do not tell him what to do 3- do not ask keyboard. Have fun and enjoy the stream
emotional_baggage: I'm a comp sci student - is it bad I have literally no idea what you're doing
ekalsuwaidi: @emotional_baggage Same LUL
puffnfresh: puffnfresh subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! can the compiler do sized vectors?
xrealyy: @emotional_baggage absolutely not, you're fine
marsroger44: do you think hackintoshing is secure in terms of file integrity?
matthewmirman: because if you have excluded middle or double negation translation from classical propositional or predicate logic forward search and backward search with enough randomization shouldn't be very different
matthewmirman: but your axioms might not be
matthewmirman: even if the inference rules
dawgwhisper007: you inspire me to work
matthewmirman: it could be the order of exploration of the axioms
Plurmorant: always backsolve puzzles
dawgwhisper007: thanks for the videos
matthewmirman: i.e. you put the wrong axiom at the bottom and you'd loop forever
puffnfresh: modus ponens is function application
f_karamazov: HSWP
brisingr1031: mp is if a is true and a implies b then b is true right?
jmc516: I learn so much shit from this stream. One day when something mad obscure comes up I’ll be chilling
puffnfresh: bottom is uninhabited here (hopefully)
matthewmirman: in constructive logic, bottom and false aren't equivalent - from bottom you can infer anything, from false you can infer only false
Usisuvach0: typing var in python LUL
marsroger44: i know the question is kinda off topic but can u answer it?
matthewmirman: false is an element of a type
matthewmirman: bottom is a type
marsroger44: do you think hackintoshing is secure in terms of file integrity?
puffnfresh: absurd : forall a. _|_ -> a
jmc516: How would you prove false != true? Is that not trivial? (Not well versed in logic)
matthewmirman: @jmc516 depends on the logic
puffnfresh: prove that a proof of false = true is uninhabited
jmc516: Aren’t false and true just definitions
puffnfresh: yeah probably
st47ik: SpaceX Starlink deployed PogChamp
matthewmirman: @puffnfresh if that is absurd, and its uninhabited, then bottom = false
DaveDreaming: I really enjoyed your interview with lex Friedman
NigerianDrugL0rd: first of all why is he not verified
railander: ye i just watched it, hopefully it is stable under bad weather and doesn't cost a leg @st47ik
NigerianDrugL0rd: twitch mafia
NigerianDrugL0rd: TriHard
railander: @NigerianDrugL0rd haHAA
wombooooo: just joined. whats george working on?
MorningScifi: Gotta write some unit tests here
l1ttlemtman: sup
l1ttlemtman: comma ai archive can't follow anymore
l1ttlemtman: too many vids
matthewmirman: you could theoretically also write a search which tries to prove the negated formula concurrently and if that one fails your search would fail
dekassssss: HeyGuys
l1ttlemtman: l1ttlemtman subscribed with Twitch Prime.
l1ttlemtman: subbed
gigafact: @l1ttlemtman I was just uploading but now that he is streaming will upload both parts together
l1ttlemtman: please unban me on discord
NigerianDrugL0rd: whats his discord
l1ttlemtman: comma ai discord
l1ttlemtman: @gigafact nice
l1ttlemtman: id upload separately but okay
matejsninja: why no IDE
l1ttlemtman: vim is better
alreye: have you bee up all night?
l1ttlemtman: does he ever read subs ?
fluzfluz: Hi georgehotz
l1ttlemtman: you know me
st47ik: True LUL
DaveDreaming: what's a sub hahaha
marsroger44: george what do you think about hackintoshing?
Plurmorant: irc for the masses monkaS
alexdickson98: do you know u have mark zuckerbergs haircut?
Usisuvach0: irc rulles
f_karamazov: If discord is toxic what is slack
hackyhacks: that applies to the entire internet. the internet was good when it was hard to use and especially post content. the difficulty acted as a stupidity filter.
Rekkeno: "don't be poor" - classic ben shapiro
alreye: functional programming over OOP?
ma3stroxq: beyler bu eleman napıyor anlayan var mı aq
l1ttlemtman: what do I have to do to get unbanned ? I tried to contact u ?
MorningScifi: I mean, this is why StackOverflow isn't Yahoo Answers. Better moderation
l1ttlemtman: why don't u use Isabelle ?
l1ttlemtman: Isabelle is nice
UzeezU: It's not nice to use people
ma3stroxq: what is he doing
marsroger44: @Rekkeno :D
DaveDreaming: proud level 2
dekassssss: https://github.com/geohot/twitchcoq
st47ik: haha
Plurmorant: never trust a language with a real name
sultantw: you still learning Unity?
l1ttlemtman: unity sucks
sk84uhlivin: Have fun today George :)
l1ttlemtman: nobody want games
st47ik: @l1ttlemtman why does unity suck? its used for more than games
st47ik: Hackerman mode
el_pirulote: john lemon FeelsBadMan
l1ttlemtman: really there is not much other than games
st47ik: @l1ttlemtman Augmented reality?
MrBankster: george will you ever work for a big tech company again?
l1ttlemtman: that's also a game
l1ttlemtman: a kids game
st47ik: k
l1ttlemtman: lol
criiscarpenter: SeemsGood
alreye: damn python is so slow
mosin_lol: sony the meme company
l1ttlemtman: there is no geohot emote ?!?!!?
criiscarpenter: No
l1ttlemtman: nooooo?
gigafact: someone should make one
euranymous: Whats your view on this @georgehotz : "Bill Gates made money by extinguishing free software and forcing users to pay him a tax just to turn our computers on. Just because the state was ready to enforce his "Intellactual Property"
marsroger44: can you show your no script settings?
st47ik: Amazon is worst NotLikeThis
fluzfluz: lul
marsroger44: lol
alreye: @euranymous is stupid because you don't have to buy a computer that runs windows....
smurfd0: bill gates gives away tooons of cash to good charities
euranymous: @alreye I am linux user my guy
alreye: @euranymous buy a computer with no OS and install a free OS
burimbushii: I bet you can do a better search engine than google :)
st47ik: i mean the worst thing now days is the anti-competitive practices and the formation of giant monopolies
ajibigad: bill gates sabi work
fluzfluz: billstein
alreye: @burimbushii LUL
euranymous: Does anybody know the past life of steve jobs?
l1ttlemtman: MrDestructoid
marsroger44: can metamath check proofs?
burimbushii: @alreye LOL
l1ttlemtman: that's the point of a proof assistant @marsroger44
MDSZilla: l1ttlemtman can you tell me what he's doing even tho I like this stuff im still pretty new ot it
fluzfluz: :))
MDSZilla: to it*
fluzfluz: lol
fluzfluz: stupid people here
slowkep: monkaS
st47ik: low quality chat again NotLikeThis
forkdb: Mentals
notmomu: yerrrrrr
slowkep: KEKW
l1ttlemtman: @mdszilla proof mathematical problems
slowkep: LUL *
fluzfluz: ty
forkdb: Chat gone mental again
fluzfluz: ahahhaa
oMythra: Georgy boii
ma3stroxq: guys pls let him work
MDSZilla: l1ttlemtman ah aight
marsroger44: looool
slowkep: Can you play stardew valley? plz dont ban me LUL
marsroger44: no refunds guys
marsroger44: ahahhaha
st47ik: that's like stealing
Plurmorant: bans are real freedom
alreye: There's no refunds
st47ik: LUL
euranymous: Thats laugh able
voodoorama: do you drink alcohol?
forkdb: Eat a frog hahahaha
oMythra: Ruthless
mosin_lol: so sub first than get banned to get money back? LUL
l1ttlemtman: but let me give you some advice. don't learn metamath
l1ttlemtman: @mdszilla
marsroger44: @l1ttlemtman do you have to transform the whole proof into metamath to let it check
marsroger44: *have
l1ttlemtman: basically yes there is a site called formalizing 100 proofs
marsroger44: why tho
marsroger44: what for? :D
alreye: Nice emacs skills LUL
l1ttlemtman: python doesn't support that. coq does. you always have to put the whole proof into the proof assistant
gmabreak: vim is great !! if you know how to quit it :p
matejsninja: @l1ttlemtman so he is improvin it right now yes?
l1ttlemtman: metamath's syntax is disgusting
l1ttlemtman: no he is working on proofing problems
marsroger44: yeah looks absolutely terrible
l1ttlemtman: yes it does
l1ttlemtman: creepy
marsroger44: terrifying
euranymous: ONE PHAT STRING
l1ttlemtman: @matejsninja answer above
alreye: @georgehotz What do you think of actuaries?
niiq: is he hacking twitch?=
marsroger44: HAHAHAHAHA
smurfd0: like yesterday? :)
gmabreak: true
matejsninja: @l1ttlemtman thanks, watchin his streams always remind me that coding is awesome tool not only to earn money but have also fun in creative way :P
srYhe: srYhe subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! sub will have emotes ?
st47ik: PogChamp
marsroger44: why not open your own streaming site
Bitsnoxx: D: LUL
Bitsnoxx: BlessRNG
l1ttlemtman: the GitHub profile pic would be ideal
niiq: BlessRNG
st47ik: BlessRNG
srYhe: FeelsGoodMan
el_pirulote: Kappa
euranymous: LUL
Plurmorant: gotta appeal to them evangelicals
haircutjimmy: haircutjimmy subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 5 months! woo!
l1ttlemtman: SMOrc
alreye: They saw you writtig a metamath parser and they said... nah
Dennjs: what boarkkey he got? Kappa
l1ttlemtman: they saw metamath syntax and said no
matthewmirman: so metamath is basically tag machines ?
st47ik: @Dennjs oh no u shouldn't ask about that
marsroger44: whats the git link to this party
alreye: @Dennjs Lol please do
Dennjs: issa joke @st47ik
l1ttlemtman: geohot/twitchcoq
st47ik: LUL
Dennjs: its a joooooke @alreye
matthewmirman: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tag_system
marsroger44: can i commit ?
matthewmirman: my hypothesis is that metamath is a language for designing what seems to be tag systems
l1ttlemtman: @marsroger44 make a pull
niiq: can u add gachiBASS
l1ttlemtman: ?
l1ttlemtman: why doesn't he go to work?
l1ttlemtman: vacation? ArgieB8
Dennjs: anyone got any ideas of what i can program just to pass time? nothing serious
alreye: @l1ttlemtman veterans day :)
matejsninja: @Dennjs anything that solves your everyday life problems
wiaK: what language is this? (.mm)
l1ttlemtman: metamath
wiaK: thanks
l1ttlemtman: syntax shit tho
l1ttlemtman: make a NLP model to program it for you
Am4teur: you kinda pretty, ngl
alreye: @Am4teur :O G..........yyy
Am4teur: im a girl dude
matthewmirman: have you seen Ollibot? http://ollibot.hyperkind.org/ollibot-0.1/ also good for building stack machines/tag automata but you get more powerful pattern matching and less absurd substitution rules
CaptCalifornia: im offended that you would do this so early
matthewmirman: so you could write search in basically the same way, and just not have to make your axioms as complicated
l1ttlemtman: oh veterans Day
l1ttlemtman: I am in Europe
l1ttlemtman: gonna have a metamath Wednesday next week
unknown_elemen: hi
wrelt: hi
euranymous: I am groot
unknown_elemen: yes u are
euranymous: i am groot
unknown_elemen: am fine
slurpwaffl: did u choose coq because u already kinda new it? I was looking at this prover called lean that syntactically was a bit easy to understand imo
slurpwaffl: https://leanprover.github.io/
wiaK: What's the goal of this?
slurpwaffl: backspace.ai
matthewmirman: One way you could characterize metamath I guess is as literally by-hand ordered logic programming with only left implication and broken substitution
ImJ4Gu4R: test
wiaK: test, always, test
Narakuwow: helloi16Derp2
matthewmirman: if you look up the literature on substructural logic programming, you might find quite a few "tactics" people have actually found useful beyond forward and backward
matthewmirman: specifically, focusing
twiggy_io: No its not
matthewmirman: https://ncatlab.org/nlab/show/focusing
fafws321: Hey dostlar
AKspirits: good morning george
haircutjimmy: do we have math nerds, programming nerds, Python nerds or other types of nerds in this chat??
snapcs1: yes
AKspirits: i enjoy python
haircutjimmy: all nerds
AKspirits: obviously
haircutjimmy: I'm a python / go nerd - enjoyed watching G do that stuff. The maths stuff i can't follow.
AKspirits: agreed haha
alreye: The screen is kinda blurry... we can't read any code
Shachilol: looks fine to me
snapcs1: looks good for me
AKspirits: maybe u have a low res on
FigurativelyVyres: Good for me also
erichtp: Looks good to me
snapcs1: PogChamp
alreye: oh shit I had it low res LUL sorry
FigurativelyVyres: 2 2 = PogChamp
Plurmorant: you ain't no bertrand russel
erk4sh: who are the person behind you?
Plurmorant: PogChamp
matthewmirman: bertrand russel had lambda calculus in principia mathematica
marsroger44: lol
Keyeh: can you prove things with emoji though?
marsroger44: proove the riemann hypothesis pls
fluzfluz: SeemsGood
marsroger44: boooom
alreye: Favorite quote from Russel "The whole problem with the world is that fools and fanatics are always so certain of themselves, and wiser people so full of doubts."
euranymous: @marsroger44 okay boomer
marsroger44: @euranymous :D
euranymous: LUL
haircutjimmy: Category: Basic Programming <- irony
marsroger44: well if not riemann there other fun problems too :D
sausainismilka: I saw a video when you wrote an exploit and hacked a computer. it was dope Kappa Kreygasm
Ham_med_Ruskindsjakken: chat help me understand, why is specifically Coq good at proving math ?
Keyeh: just for practice you can solve the poincaré conjecture
marsroger44: screw that one
marsroger44: perelman already did
marsroger44: too late @Keyeh
Keyeh: yeah i know, thats why i said for practice
sausainismilka: I wouldn't be surprised, if you code day and night Kappa
liivius: !uptime
Keyeh: why solve riemann when you can solve car automation PogChamp
sausainismilka: have a good day geo. cya later.
alreye: at what time do you usually go to sleep?
erichtp: Chicken tendies PogChamp
marsroger44: :D
erichtp: :)
euranymous: BAAAMMM!
marsroger44: booooom
warpoit: peace have a BLESS DAY and good day at work.
sausainismilka: lmfaooo
snapcs1: LOL
NonTrivial778: we need linear algebra proof then LUL
joaofoliveira: gmorning George!
Emanuelsson123: Cheers
marsroger44: well said
Plurmorant: KKona 7
gigafact: thanks for the steam George!
alreye: No freedom in chat tho
Keyeh: KKona unite
marsroger44: boooooooom
Keyeh: LMAO
st47ik: LUL
sausainismilka: i don't like math but i'm watching because i'm interested
NonTrivial778: LUL
joaofoliveira: yeah but this is no America, this is everywhere, freedom everywhere
joaofoliveira: :P
marsroger44: savage
erichtp: LUL
snapcs1: LOOOL
Ham_med_Ruskindsjakken: haha :D
NonTrivial778: tsodinFeels
euranymous: I wanna see proof of (a b)^2 = a^2 b^2 2ab
st47ik: SpaceX Starlink launched PogChamp
BigBrainDota: cool of you to not disable whispers
snapcs1: that kid is so mad :D
marsroger44: hahahhha
euranymous: Any mods online??
alreye: LUL
Pryetranka: LUL
neca420: NotLikeThis
notice_me_OpieOP: sup y'all cmonBruh /
sausainismilka: this kid is retarted and mad lmfaooo
MonkaSupreme: Can you proof sqrt(2) > 1
BigBrainDota: LUL
Attlantiz_: hey george. whats the high brown stuff today
Emanuelsson123: LUL
matthewmirman: or strong normalization for simply typed lambda calculus
marsroger44: are u gonna buy the new mac pro?
matthewmirman: that'd be chill
st47ik: <3
anup_kodlekere: yo george
Plurmorant: LUL
joaofoliveira: greetings from Portugal George!
Triphasic: Yo
Satanicus7: KEKW
The_Tyrant: george any email or way i can contact you please
sausainismilka: bagginer lmfaooo
Plurmorant: worse than a fuck you
PanicPoint: $50 for a life coaching session
BigBrainDota: fak LUL
xaxaar: that was definitely a bunch of dicks
dalex_live: it was a hydra Kappa
anup_kodlekere: whens the next stream?
MDSZilla: @georgehotz careful while opening if its against TOS there's always a risk
MonkaSupreme: it was dick hydra
Triphasic: I’m going to give a presentation about AI in cars this Wednesday in school
Pryetranka: whisper review PogChamp
anup_kodlekere: whens the next stream?
bebytesback: @georgehotz Was your talk at UCSD recorded?
MDSZilla: It is against nudity graphics so yeah LUL
Attlantiz_: whisperr georgee
marsroger44: how is the cloud
Triphasic: Thanks man haha I won’t say anything about AI anymore 🤐
Attlantiz_: click
sausainismilka: LITHUAANIIAAA MY COUNTRY.
Triphasic: Look up Belgium lol
Triphasic: My country is a joke
Attlantiz_: Look up portugal
NonTrivial778: Can you understand this math https://dcc.fceia.unr.edu.ar/sites/default/files/uploads/materias/AL2013-PR5.pdf
ekalsuwaidi: Look up Dubai :)
fluzfluz: greez from switzerland
MDSZilla: What about Starlink any opinions?
ReDD_TV_: Denmark :D
Attlantiz_: do you like it :P ?
Triphasic: For real? What’d you visit in Belgium?
Plurmorant: math not in english DansGame
renatobarresi: look up paraguay, the happiest country in the wolrd
marsroger44: ahhahahhaa
SCVready60: LUL
notice_me_OpieOP: georgehotz your bttv emote game is weak george cmonBruh
Attlantiz_: did you go lisbon george? or porto?
alreye: have you been to south america?
anup_kodlekere: youve been around
MDSZilla: Starlink George Any Opinions?
Triphasic: Lmaooooo Manneken Pis
Emanuelsson123: LUL
kingkong3211: come to the UK
revolutionist123: LUL come to Greece
notice_me_OpieOP: yelled at george BibleThump
ekalsuwaidi: 3Head Bruv
takroli3: come to turkey :")
Attlantiz_: dont go to north UK
gingersniffer: im from newcastle Pog
zynsmurf: tbh mcdonalds closed at 10pm seems weird af
bsx1123: Netherlands?
speedle123: @gingersniffer i'm nearby pog
anup_kodlekere: come to Goa
Maty_Kapsa: Prague?
DomisDream: @georgehotz Tips for Programing beginers? Just started to study programing on university
Attlantiz_: george hates latin countries boooo
dalex_live: vncouver
MDSZilla: Hi from Pakistan as well ;)
HugoDerruci3: come to Brazil.... just kidding, dom't come here
Satanicus7: Czech Republic?
jbyte1988: PERU
DaDoDe: Japan?
harm243: huh?
birrdd: birrddYes
notice_me_OpieOP: come to narnia PogChamp
takroli3: turkey?
bsx1123: Amsterdam?
GaNDyRaC: Russia?
anup_kodlekere: should do this more often
MDSZilla: Pakistan ? :P
notice_me_OpieOP: moon?
sausainismilka: george without food not george lmao.
alreye: Been to Brazil?
Attlantiz_: have you been to madeira george
NonTrivial778: Argentina
anup_kodlekere: Goa?
Tsoding: LUL
MonkaSupreme: mother russia
zoki_macola: Serbia
cutza: México?
stalys_: india?
ekalsuwaidi: Dubai is safe
fluzfluz: Swiss?
GaNDyRaC: Welcome to Russia, comrade KappaPride
BigBrainDota: have you been to most of europe?
marsroger44: are you gonna stream tomorrow?
Attlantiz_: have you been to azores
kingkong3211: come to somalia its fun
Maty_Kapsa: I had the best time in Vietnam, can reccomend
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: come to thailand Kappa
MDSZilla: Youtube Swat Valley Pakistan its beautiful its not just war and stuff
marsroger44: lol
Attlantiz_: hahaha lmao somalia
BigBrainDota: KEKW
notice_me_OpieOP: come to mars :)
anup_kodlekere: well you've been around
ffthgezgxjkndd: seychelles?
punj4b: Italy?
karl_mundt: Ever been in Germany?
MonkaSupreme: come to Germany
takroli3: turkey is safety but you should travel with turk friend
fluzfluz: lol
NonTrivial778: Come to Venezuela you'll be happy Kappa
alreye: That place looks scary
BigBrainDota: @takroli3 that doesnt sound safe lmao
tornix98: come to Taiwan the home of semiconductors
ekalsuwaidi: monkaS
steven_dahill301: i was here
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: Socialist dream LUL
st47ik: ever went to Africa?
alreye: been to Colombia?
anup_kodlekere: you should go to columbia lol
MDSZilla: You need to go to Iceland its freaking awesome
erichtp: Ever go to Jordan?
Plurmorant: vertically integrated company PogChamp
ekalsuwaidi: Go to south korea
lefg7: greece
Attlantiz_: george doesnt like latin countries booo jk
alreye: North Korea?
punj4b: ever go to Italy?
anup_kodlekere: North Korea
BigBrainDota: LUL
kingkong3211: North Korea?
DaDoDe: LOL
st47ik: LUL
marsroger44: looool
ekalsuwaidi: LUL
birrdd: lmfao
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: haha
jbyte1988: VISIT AREQUIPA
kytos1k: LUL
stalys_: DuckerZ
Attlantiz_: north korea lmao
fluzfluz: lol
Plurmorant: @wegotatwitcheroverhere gotta go Just Chatting to get that partner
Triphasic: LUL
Kuunih: Spain?
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: DONT
Attlantiz_: Kappa
anup_kodlekere: Columbia
alreye: Colombia?
jbyte1988: VISIT AREQUIPA!
Attlantiz_: what unis do you like in the UK george?
Mate12392: Have you ever been to Hungary?
hue88: you can go use facebook instead of instagram if u are pissed off
notice_me_OpieOP: have you even been to mars george? BibleThump
revolutionist123: wtf isbthis earth is flat
MonkaSupreme: Will you go to space?
hue88: LUL
renatobarresi: paraguayy
SpekKas123: Go to lithuania
uiq3eu: Come to Poland to meet Polish hackers!
mickowale: korea
steven_dahill301: have you been to cuba?
Attlantiz_: george can you check if the computer science course in Warwick is good xD
anup_kodlekere: Arctic vs Antarctica?
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: George flat earther?
hue88: still flat for me
MDSZilla: Another really beautiful place to visit in Pakistan is Skardu
takkeo: Morocco ?
punj4b: Italy?
NonTrivial778: Is this shit real ? http://www.redusers.com/noticias/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/lifes_good1.jpg
fluzfluz: hostel
alreye: Romania?
erichtp: Romania ?
bsx1123: Warsaw is a very nice city
wall_streeter: Romania?
kytos1k: St.Petersburg is n1ce
revolutionist123: LUL nice reason
HugoDerruci3: The only good thing here in Brazil is the coffee. Americans don't know how to make good coffee
jbyte1988: AREQUIPA
Purschtus: thoughts on German automotive industry?
ekalsuwaidi: Do u play video games?
anup_kodlekere: Iraq
Attlantiz_: george likes 2nd world countries :Kappa: jk
alreye: Beautiful ladies in Romania
takroli3: what do u think about turkey be honest
GaNDyRaC: maybe Belarus?
MDSZilla: Google Images Shangrila Resort Skardu its also a place I visited recently in Pakistan its awesome
st47ik: @georgehotz have u seen this https://www.kura.tech/products
Attlantiz_: ahahahha xD
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: D:
jbyte1988: VISIT AREQUIPAA
Attlantiz_: whats kura
NonTrivial778: WutFace
anup_kodlekere: sounds like qira
Attlantiz_: oh thats fancy
K177Music: LUL
marsroger44: wowi wooww
st47ik: Augmented reality is here Kreygasm
marsroger44: whoop whoop
euranymous: Have you been to Nepal??
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: google glass?
st47ik: specs are crazy
Attlantiz_: buy me one of those glasses Kappa
visudo20179c: sup Geohot
MDSZilla: It starts mid 2020 it said below purchase options
Plurmorant: NotLikeThis
alreye: Just pre-order it
notice_me_OpieOP: do it PogChamp
st47ik: 2020 is the future LUL
Attlantiz_: do you like thinkpads george? macbooks seem a bit expensive
MDSZilla: Apple tried but it didnt work so they stopped
yaus_baus: good morning george
notice_me_OpieOP: 🍏
Attlantiz_: does it suffer from burn in?
amratesh: 👁️
Plurmorant: mailing list LUL
yaus_baus: good morning chat
st47ik: Kura seems like a good company
BigBrainDota: what is it
MDSZilla: Apple was going to use Micro LED in Series 5 watch but they switched for OLED
NonTrivial778: What can I do if I have an IQ of 50?
Attlantiz_: have you seen microsoft's arm chip
jbyte1988: AREQUIPA
RSPwner_: do you use screen in bash for different tabs?
Attlantiz_: tmux I think
visudo20179c: its tmux @RSPwner_
RSPwner_: oo
RSPwner_: ty
st47ik: PogChamp
visudo20179c: yep, you can get his tmux config file somewhere too
st47ik: north star are so chunky tho LUL
Plurmorant: that's a steal wtf PogChamp
erichtp: Do you still have that 3D printed head set
alreye: yes
leander_ms: monteAK
Attlantiz_: have you seen microsoft's arm chip on the surface x george? thoughts?
visudo20179c: thats a subscriber only question ;)
yaus_baus: dotfiles https://github.com/geohot/configuration
visudo20179c: ^
notice_me_OpieOP: it's a virus :)
Plurmorant: ultra-low cost MonkaSupreme
MDSZilla: It probably comes with the software
SlaterUSA: @georgehotz see if you can fiddle with the HTML and un-disable that thing you can't add to cart :D
Plurmorant: monkaS
SlaterUSA: no on the other page
yaus_baus: how long hes been streaming?
visudo20179c: few minutes
yaus_baus: fsho fsho
tornix98: !uptime
Sheggellz: Who shut my mounth yesterday guys
Sheggellz: mouth*
Plurmorant: puzzle solved PogChamp
SlaterUSA: ur mom?
st47ik: LUL
Attlantiz_: nooooooooo
fluzfluz: cya
leander_ms: D:
notmomu: where you going
st47ik: North Star stream soon PogChamp
karl_mundt: Thanks!
visudo20179c: we love you Geohot
kytos1k: cya
Attlantiz_: have you seen microsoft's arm chip?
Betazz: nooooo
notmomu: don't violate stay big homie
zgamer0123: nooooo
Maty_Kapsa: dude you are the best
matejsninja: thanks buddy you motivaated me to make a small fix in a project :P
MDSZilla: What about starlink Kappa
Triphasic: Bye George ✌️
boss_ev: thk you
st47ik: thanks George bye VoHiYo
fluzfluz: we love you Geohot
Attlantiz_: bye
takkeo: Bye
balkibee: HeyGuys
yaus_baus: byebye
notmomu: i love you bye
kingkong3211: bye
MDSZilla: Aighty laters
leander_ms: u work?
zgamer0123: bye george, ur amazing
Betazz: bb
unluckychickenn: bye <3
MonkaSupreme: :(
Attlantiz_: rip he dead
DaDoDe: F
notmomu: damn :(